Special Collections Research Center
- Project Files, 1951-1978; 1
  - Lucey, John and Mari, 1977; 7732; extent; note1; note2 (Box 45, Folder 404, Item 3)
  - Foster, David, 1979; 7801; note1; note2 (Box 46, Folder 405)
- Professional and Personal, 1955-1978; 2
  - MC 00000 Subseries 01.01, 1951; 1
    - Daily Financial Ledger, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Othertype 550)
  - MC 00000 Subseries 01.02, 1952; 2
    - Scott, Correspondence Prior to 1959, 1955-1959 (Box 58, Othertype 551)
- Microfilm, 1969-1979; 3
  - Kenneth McCoy Scott, 4250 (Box 63, Othertype 1)
    Sessions 32-38